Indiana University School of Continuing Studies records, 1971-2008 C339
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University School of Continuing Studies records
1971-2008
1989-2004
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. School of Continuing Studies
C339
5.8 cubic feet 7 boxes
Initially founded in 1970 as the Indiana University Division of Continuing Education, the School of Continuing Studies was established in 1975 to offer opportunities in education for students who were unable to attend traditional formal university programs. Collection includes correspondence, subject files, catalogs, reports, marketing information, and financial records.
Access Restrictions
Student files series is closed to researchers at this time.
Advance notice required for access.
Administrative History
Realizing the need for educational alternatives for those unable to attend traditional on-campus classes, the School of Continuing Studies was established in 1975 to offer further educational opportunities to individuals who worked full-time, had families, were homebound by illness, were in the military, or were in prison. Dean Dr. Robert Richey (Dean from 1975-1978) at the time noted the need for alternative methods of delivery to students rather than the traditional in-class lecture system. He cited alternate mechanisms for delivery of content such as cable television and video cassettes, the radio-television department, the eight campuses around the state, and the already established 130 university independent study programs.
In the early days of its existence (1975-1976), the system wide school was comprised of the Division of Extended Studies, Labor Education and Research, and the Division of Continuing Education. By fall 1977, all eight IU campuses offered the Associate of General Studies and the Bachelor of General Studies degrees.
The organizational structure of the school evolved under the direction of Dean James E. Weigand (1979-1993). Focusing upon the use of independent study, he fused the Independent Study Division and the External Degree Program into the Division of Extended Studies. He furthermore approved the formation of the New Division of Professional development, which sought to develop nondegree programs for professional associations and business. Additionally, during the course of the 1980s, the School of Continuing Studies established programs in Saudi Arabia, South Africa, Malaysia, and Iran.
Kathy Krendl replaced Weigand as dean in 1994 and brought a focused commitment to the use of technology for the delivery of instruction, and furthermore sought to establish a distance education plan. During her tenure until 1996, the school implemented the Multicampus Technology Project, which created state-of-the-art videoconferencing facilities on each of the IU campuses. She was followed by Howard Mehlinger as interim dean, and then Jeremy Dunning as dean in the fall of 1999.
In 2008 the School of Continuing Studies is under the direction of Judy Wertheim and is now comprised of the Office of Academic Programs, the Office of Financial Administration, Instructional Design and Development, Technology Support, the Office of Learner Services, and the Office of Marketing and Communications. In addition, to the school's General Studies degree – either the association of arts or the bachelor of arts – students are also given the opportunity to earn several certificates to further develop their career skills. In addition to credit programs, the School of Continuing Studies also offers an Undergraduate Nondegree Program for students wishing to update their jobs skills or looking to prepare themselves before entering a degree seeking program, and Professional Development and Lifelong Learning non-credit courses for those seeking to advance their career or simply seeking further education. Initiated in 1972 and co-sponsored by the Indiana University Alumni Association and the School of Continuing Studies, Mini University is another major program which seeks to provide a unique educational and vacation experience for adults. Another major initiative is the Leadership Bloomington- Monroe County program which is designed to teach skills to those seeking to lead in their workplace and community.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into five series: Administrative files, Publications, Non-credit program/ Lifelong Learning course files, Lifelong Learning day trips, and Student files.
Scope and Content Note
The Continuing Studies records are organized into five series. The first, Administrative files (1980-1998), is a small series containing miscellaneous administrative information from only selective dates. Materials include reports, information relating to advertizing and marketing, and binders which include information such as mission statements, organizational charts, annual reports, calendars, program information, and records on Mini University (see also IU Archives Collection C338 for the records of Mini University).
The second series, Publications (1971-2008), includes the biannual course catalogs released by the School of Continuing Studies. The catalogs include general information about the program; available courses including information on the instructor, fees and locations; and information on a variety of other Continuing Studies programs.
The Non-credit/ Lifelong Learning Course files (1981-2004) are arranged alphabetically by keyword in the course title such as gardening and music. Materials include course summaries, syllabi, course handouts, various clippings relating to the subject matter of the course and correspondence relating to the scheduling of the course.
The Lifelong Learning Day Trips (1982-2002) series is organized alphabetically by location. Materials include financial documents such as budgets and invoices, various publications and pamphlets relating to the destination of the trip, schedules, contracts, class rosters, correspondence relating to the planning of the event.
The final series, Student Files (1995-2004) contains student profile and grade point average statistical information. This series is closed to researchers.
Separated Material
19 photographs were pulled from the records relating to the Continuing Studies trip in 1999 to the West Baden Springs Hotel and French Lick Resort. Photographs show participants in the hotel, on the resort grounds, and in the gardens. Contact the Archives Photographs Curator for additional information.
Acquisition Information
Accession 2008/003 and 2008/036
Distance Education --Indiana --History --Sources.; Adult Education --Indiana --History --Sources.; Continuing Education --Indiana --History --Sources.; Indiana University. Division of Continuing Education; Indiana University. School of Continuing Studies -- Archives; Indiana University. School of Continuing Studies -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University. School of Continuing Studies -- History -- Sources; Indiana University. School of Continuing Studies -- Administration
- Administrative Files, 1980-1998; undated (Box 1)
  - Task Force to Study the School of Continuing Studies, 1980 (Box 1)
    General
    (2 folders)
  - Noncredit Program Ads, 1985-2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Marketing Information Noncredit Course Program, 1989-1998 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies Binder, 1990-1994 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies- Master Copy binder, 1990-1994 (Box 1)
  - Implementation Plan for Achieving Our New Vision, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Office Christmas Party, undated (Box 1)
- Publications, 1971-2008
  - Noncredit Program for Adults- Catalogs (Box 1)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1)
    - 1972-1976 (Box 1)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 1)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 1)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 1)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 1)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 2)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 2)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 2)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 2)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 2)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 2)
    - 2006-2008 (Box 2)
- Non-credit Program/ Lifelong Learning Course Files, 1981-2004; undated
  - Abraham: A Model of Faith?- Ackerman N957, 2000-2002 (Box 2)
  - Two Pianos-Four Hands: Trip to Actors Theatre of Louisville – 04SJ041HU, Spring 2004 (Box 2)
  - The Miser: Trip to Actors' Theatre Louisville – 04FJ041HU, Fall 2004 (Box 2)
  - The Aging Eye and Vision Loss – 04FS011HU, Fall 2004 (Box 2)
  - Introductory Algebra- N800, Fall 1992 (Box 2)
  - The American Detective Novel, Fall 1991 (Box 2)
  - American Impressionists- N894, Spring 1995 (Box 2)
  - American Presidents: The Great, Near Great, and the Rest- Katz NA007, Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - The American Short Story- N959, 1998 (Box 2)
  - American Sign Language: An Introduction- Cornwell NA016, Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - American Sign Language- N490, 1988-1996 (Box 2)
  - An Antique Collector's Primer- N782, Fall 1991 (Box 2)
  - An Antique Collector's Primer- N782, Fall 1996 (Box 2)
  - Becoming an Antique Detective- N846, undated (Box 2)
  - Dating Antique and Collectible Quilts- N782, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Apache Worlds- N984, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Archaeological Discoveries- Matthew Goodrum NA030, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Archaeology, First Encounters: Columbus, Native Americans, and the Birth of the Modern World- N994, Fall 2000 (Box 2)
  - Armchair Travel: France- N935, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Armchair Travel: Greece N935, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Armchair Travel: Insider's Guide to Germany- N935, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Armchair Travel: Land of the Ascending Dragon- N935, Fall 2000 (Box 2)
  - The Art and Biblical Message of Marc Chagall- Van Buskirk N894, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Art History Courses- Mazelle van Buskirk, 1977-1989 (Box 2)
  - Astronomy Course and Observatory Activities, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Basketball Noncredit Course, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Beekeeping- Hegeman N924, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Beowulf- N966, Fall 2000 (Box 2)
  - Biblical Faith: Claiming the Promise – 04SH109HU, Spring 2004 (Box 2)
  - Bird Study, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Borges and Beyond: The Latin American Short Story- Friedman N902, 1998 (Box 2)
  - British Monarchy: Tradition, Mystique – 04FH160HU, Fall 2004 (Box 2)
  - Brown County Playhouse, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Building Strong Family Relationships – 04SS201HU, Spring 2004 (Box 2)
  - Butterflies and Butterfly Plants- Belth N838, Spring 1999 (Box 2)
  - Career Management Series- Sgambelluri N119, Spring 1996 (Box 2)
  - Chemistry for Cowards- Marianne Feller, Spring 1989 (Box 2)
  - Cicada Mania – 04SS501HU, Fall 2004 (Box 2)
  - Never Shall I Forget…Echoes of the Civil War- N909 Cindy May, Spring 2001 (Box 2)
  - Clues from the Cloth: Indiana Quilts- William Lawrence N782, Spring 1996 (Box 2)
  - College 101: A Guide for Parents – 04ST051HU, February 29, 2004 (Box 2)
  - How to Troubleshoot a Troublesome Computer- Land N878, Spring 1995 (Box 2)
  - Confidence Factor- Nelson N858, Fall 1993 (Box 2)
  - Conflict and Confrontation- Hughes N638, Fall 1996 (Box 2)
  - Cooking with Herbs- Houston, Fall 1991 (Box 2)
  - Creative Writing: Fiction- Marvin N567, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Effective Cycling- N897, Spring 1995 (Box 2)
  - Desktop Publishing- Volen, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Drawing and Painting- Troy N134, Fall 1989 (Box 2)
  - Eat, Drink and Be Merry: Books in the Lilly Collection about Food and Drink- N933, undated (Box 2)
  - Economics Made Easy – 04SH421HU, Spring 2004 (Box 2)
  - The Edible Forest and Field- N815, Spring 1992 (Box 2)
  - From the Banks of the Nile: Egyptian Shows at the Indiana University Art Museum- N592, Spring 1998 (Box 2)
  - Election 2004: Candidates Strategies – 04FH120HU, Fall 2004 (Box 2)
  - Electronic Library- Malcom N907, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Embracing Diversity- Bradshaw N876, Fall 1994 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Issues, Meadowood Program- N732, Spring 1989 (Box 2)
  - Ethics in America, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Falls of the Ohio: Fossils and Rocks- Comer N552, Fall 1998 (Box 2)
  - Fashion and the Arts- Rowold N943, Fall 1997 (Box 2)
  - Never the Same Old Story: The Art of Short Fiction- Cancelled- Watson NA006, Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Film Studies Courses, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - The Movie Musical- NS725, Spring 1993 (Box 2)
  - The "Reel" America: The United States in Popular Film, Part 1- Yaudes NA025, Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Your Path to Financial Security: It's Easier Than You Think!- N980, Fall 1999 (Box 2)
  - Financial Planning, Estate Planning- N366, 1989-1992 (Box 2)
  - Financial Planning of Retirement Years (Estate Planning, Trust, Power of Attorney, Guardianship, etc.), Fall 1983 (Box 2)
  - Financial Strategies- Allen, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Financial Strategies for Successful Retirement- N287, Fall 1996 (Box 2)
  - Exercise Techniques for Strength Development- N771, Fall 1994 (Box 2)
  - Fitness for Adults with Physical Limitations- N748, Fall 1993 (Box 2)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright: Building a Legacy – 04FH092HU, Fall 2004 (Box 2)
  - French Culture and Cuisine - Dempster N964, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Fundraising, 1994-1998 (Box 2)
  - Gardening- Burnham, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Gardening- Burton, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Garden Course- Sissinghurst N975, undated (Box 2)
  - Gardening Courses, 1988-1995 (Box 2)
  - Gardening for Butterflies – N838, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Gardening in a Season of Short Days – Clay N856, Fall 1997 (Box 2)
  - Gardening in the Grand Style: The Gilded Age of American Gardens – Bracalente N975, Spring 2000 (Box 2)
  - Gardening on the Wild Side – Clay N786, Spring 1992 (Box 2)
  - Garden of the World – Peterson N595, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Beginning Vegetable Gardening- N806, Winter 1992 (Box 2)
  - Blooms in Bloomington: Fall Perennials – Burnham NA017, Fall 2001 (Box 2)
  - Edible Indiana- Bertoccio N815, Spring 1994 (Box 2)
  - An Evening with Gourds- N920, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Fall Blooming Perennials- Burnham N883, Fall 1995 (Box 2)
  - Fall Blooming Perennials- Burnham N883, Fall 1998 (Box 2)
  - Get Growing Now – N740, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Guardians of the Garden Sunflowers- Heiser N947, undated (Box 2)
  - Herb Gardening and Harvesting- Bean N757, undated (Box 2)
  - Lore of the Bulbs – Bracalente NA018, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Native Plants- Clay N786, Spring 1994 (Box 2)
  - Perennials for Shade Gardening – Burnham N946, Spring 1998 (Box 2)
  - Perennials for Shade Gardening – Burnham N946, Spring 1999 (Box 2)
  - Perennial Plant Combinations – Burnham N649, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Successful Gardening with Perennial Flowers – N649, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Using Perennial Plants in Flourishing Borders – 04SH107HU, March 29, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Genealogy – N722, Spring 1989 (Box 3)
  - Genealogy, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Genealogy – N722, Spring 1991 (Box 3)
  - Genealogy – N722, Spring 1993 (Box 3)
  - Genealogy – N722, Spring 1994 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Genealogy- N722, Spring 1995 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Genealogy- Devore N722, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Research Tools for Family History – Cattelona N927, undated (Box 3)
  - Understanding Genetic Diseases – Koch N982, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Geological Shake and Bake! Earthquakes – 04SS401HU, March 2, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Geology of Indiana – Comer N983, Fall 1999 (Box 3)
  - Conversational German – Starr N079, 1998 (Box 3)
  - German for Travel: Conversational German – N079, 1988-1990 (Box 3)
  - Getting Organized – Nelson N476, Spring 1995 (Box 3)
  - Get to Know Your Community – N912, 1995 (Box 3)
  - GMAT Student Handouts, 1989 (Box 3)
  - GMAT Workshop – NT004, Fall 2001 (Box 3)
  - Preparing for the GMAT – N767, undated (Box 3)
  - Goethe's Faust, Part I – Piedmont N956, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Golf – Bowman N456, Spring 2001 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Golf, Session 1a and 1b – 04SG011HU, April 29, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Golf, Session 2a and 2b – 04SG021HU, May 24, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Golf, Session 3a and 3b – 04SG035HU, June 28, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Intermediate Golf Session 1 – 04SG110HU, April 20, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Intermediate Golf Session 2 – 04SG210HU, May 25, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Intermediate Golf Session 3 – 04SG310HU, June 29, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Take the Grr Out of Grammer – Steiner N758, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Preparing for the GRE McNair Scholars Course, Fall 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Preparing for the GRE, Short Course for NSSLHA, Spring 1996-1998 (Box 3)
  - Preparing for the GRE Subject Exam in Psychology – McKinley, Fall 1992 (Box 3)
  - Preparing for the GRE SROP Course, Spring 1994-1997 (Box 3)
  - GRE Workshop (Section 1 and 2) – Warren NT002, Fall 2001 (Box 3)
  - GRE Workshop I – 04ST131HU, February 14, 2004 (Box 3)
  - GRE Workshop II – 04ST041HU, March 27, 2004 (Box 3)
  - GRE Prep Section1a – 04FT131HU, September 18, 2004 (Box 3)
  - GRE Prep Section 2a – 04FT041HU, October 16, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Great Books, 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Great Books, undated (Box 3)
  - Great Books, class lists, 1984-1994 (Box 3)
  - Great Books Program, Historical File, 1984-1986 (Box 3)
  - Great Books Foundation, Ordering Books, 1984-1993 (Box 3)
  - Great Books Table Tents, undated (Box 3)
  - Great Books Training, undated (Box 3)
  - Greek Art – Marer-Banasik N874, Spring 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Beginning Guitar – Williams, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Courses Involving Guns and Shooting – Mills N768, Spring 1984 (Box 3)
  - Historic American Interiors – Cook N723, Spring 1989 (Box 3)
  - Happy Birthday Hoagy! – N987, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Home Owner Landscape Design – Schrader N616, Spring 1994 (Box 3)
  - Images of Mary Magdalene – 04FH130HU, September 21, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Improving Your Memory – Nelson N835, Fall 1995 (Box 3)
  - Improving Your Publication – McEntire N788, Spring 1991 (Box 3)
  - Indiana's European Roots – 04FH150HU, October 6, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Gold! – 04SS301HU, May 20, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Indians – Edmunds N921, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Limestone: From Quarry to Mill – 04FJ031HU, October 14, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Private Lives: Trip to the Indiana Repertory Theatre – 04SJ021HU, March 28, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Can Insurance Help – Belth N934, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Planning for a Long Life…Can Insurance Help? – Belth N934, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Interior Design Fundamentals and Fun – Landis N945, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Interior Design: What They Don't Teach – 04SH110HU, May 3, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Interior Design: What They Don't Teach – 04FH110HU, September 13, 2004 (Box 3)
  - An Exploration of Irish History: From Patrick to Partition – Coulter NA003, Fall 2001 (Box 3)
  - Who Are the Irish?: Depictions in 20th Century Literature – Owens NA004, Fall 2001 (Box 3)
  - Many Faces of Islamic Revivalism – Jacques NA053, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Italian Cuisine - N160, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Italian for Travelers – N014, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Italian for Travelers 04SL321HU, February 2, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Italian for Travelers Course Materials – N014, 1998 (Box 3)
  - It's Not Whether You Win or Lose – Hartman N781, Spring 1993 (Box 3)
  - IU Archives: Rarities and Oddities – 04FH140HU, October 16, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IU Authors' Series: Claude Clegg – 04SH131HU, February 28, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IU Author's Series: Jan Shipps – 04SH141HU, March 27, 2004 (Box 3)
  - IU Authors' Series: Jeffery Wolin – 04SH151HU, April 24, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Pollock: The Greatest American Painter? – Young NA005, Fall 2001 (Box 3)
  - The Story of Jacob – Ackerman N957, Fall 1999 (Box 3)
  - Japanese Language and Culture – 04FL031HU, September 27, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Japan through Modern Eyes – Smith N925, Spring 1997 (Box 3)
  - Discovering Bloomington's Jazz Scene – Harbison NA052, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Jazz – Baker N985, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Jewelry: Ancient to Modern – Cristol N841, Spring 1993 (Box 3)
  - Jews in America – N977, Fall 1999 (Box 3)
  - Journal Writing – Myers N646, Fall 1996 (Box 3)
  - Keeping Your Mind Active – 04SS601HU, April 20, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Kinsey Institute: 50 Years – N923, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lessons à la Lovejoy – Lawrence N846, Fall 1993 (Box 3)
  - Noncredit Courses at the Lilly Library, 1990-1996 (Box 3)
  - Treasures of the Lilly Library – N707, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Limestone Above and Below Ground – N829, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Limestone Headstones, From the Files of Don Carmony, undated (Box 3)
  - Use of Limestone in the Garden – Williams N616, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Literature of the Bible – Ackerman N512, Spring 1989-2001 (Box 3)
  - Redesigning Little Women – Nordloh NA037, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Tuning into Lotus: America's Award Winning Music Festival – Stone NA012, Fall 2001 (Box 3)
  - Management Skills Program – Sgambelluri, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Mayas, Aztecs, Incas, and Ancient Civilizations of Americas, undated (Box 3)
  - Media, Politics and the 2004 Presidential Election – 04SH108HU, March 1, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Ultimate Memory – Nelson N835, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Midwestern Fictions- Gray N791, undated (Box 3)
  - Mission to Mars – 04FS501HU, September 21, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Monroe County History, Knowing Our Past – Murray N997, Fall 2000 (Box 4)
  - Beginning Mountaineering, Winter 1992 (Box 4)
  - Mushrooms – N903, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Music for the Listener: Music Appreciation – Gillespie N653, Fall 2000 (Box 4)
  - Buddy, Beatles and Bob – Gass NA039, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Experiences with Music in Concert – Lathom N653, Fall 1995 (Box 4)
  - Mozart the Inventor: A Study of Opera – Glen N873, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Rock and Roll Explodes – Gass N890, 2000 (Box 4)
  - The Romantic in Music – 04FM223HU, September 23, 2004 (Box 4)
  - World Music – Smith N976, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Native American Crafts: Rugs and Blankets – N954, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Changing Image of the Native American in Popular Culture- Cape NA009, Fall 2001 (Box 4)
  - Natural History Regulation – Willard N958, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Introduction to Network Technology and Novell Netware System Administration, Spring 1995 (Box 4)
  - Nostalgia: The Search for the Good Old Days – Sherayko N940, Fall 1997 (Box 4)
  - Not So Simple Shakers: An Introduction – Lawrence N938, Fall 1997 (Box 4)
  - Nuts and Bolts of Managing People – N926, 1996 (Box 4)
  - NYC's Melting Pot – Katz NA007, 2001 (Box 4)
  - This Old House: Restoring Three Historic Homes – 04SH106HU, April 29, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Opera Appreciation – N942, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Opera of Guiseppe Verdi- Hart N873, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Introduction to Opera – Glen NA011, Fall 2001 (Box 4)
  - A Night at the Opera – Glen NA010, Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - Parliamentary Procedure – Harnack N819, Spring 1993 (Box 4)
  - Pedometer Walking for Fitness – 04FS161HU, October 2, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Photoshop and Scanning Workshop – Rhodes N936, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Picture Book Creation – 04SH623HU, February 12, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Playwriting – Cebulska, Spring 1994 (Box 4)
  - About Face: 200 Years of Portraits – Foster, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Positive Listening – DiSilvestro N563, Fall 1995 (Box 4)
  - Powerful Speaking for Women – Nelson, Fall 1993 (Box 4)
  - Power Walking for Fitness – N718, Spring 1995 (Box 4)
  - Pride and Prejudice: Trip to the Indiana Repertory Theatre – 04FJ021HU, October 3, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Problems of the 20th Century: Nationalism – Evans N992, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Proposal Writing, 1981-1997 (Box 4)
  - Applied Performance Psychology – Curtis N812, Fall 1992 (Box 4)
  - Public Discussion, Meadowood – NA023, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Public Discussion, MCL – 04SP011HU, February 10, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Public Discussion, Meadowood – 04SP021HU, February 18, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Public Discussion, Meadowood – 04FP021HU, February 28, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Public Discussion Opportunities, Spring 1988 (Box 4)
  - Getting It Out There: Essential Steps for Publishing – 04SH061HU, April 10, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Joy of Quilting – Dobson N673, Winter 1992 (Box 4)
  - Recycle the Garden! – Percival N773, Spring 1994 (Box 4)
  - Religion Outside the American Mainstream, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Restoration Therapy – Burns N785, Spring 1992 (Box 4)
  - The RET Approach to Taking Charge of Your Life – Isaacs, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Russian Short Story - 04SH021HU, February 4, 2004 (Box 4)
  - A Russian Romance: Tchaikovsky's Opera – 04FM041HU, October 21, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Preparing for the SAT, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Preparing for the SAT, Spring 1995 (Box 4)